http://www.botanus.com/ordering/your-privacy

Categories
Toggle Navigation
Home
Fall 2020 View All Fall 2020 Hoe Hoe Hoe SaleGift CardsFlour GardenEarth Friendly Garden Tools & SuppliesOrganic Body CareGreeting CardsBotanus Children of Haiti JewelryOrganic Herb & Vegetable SeedsContact UsAbout Us View All About Us The Botanus StoryMay We IntroduceOur GardensBotanus in the NewsWe Guarantee to WOW!Botanus PresentationsBotanus on FacebookBotanus on PinterestBotanus on YouTubeFun Stuff View All Fun Stuff Garden Gnome ContestOrdering View All Ordering Download Our Current CatalogueRequest a Catalogue & NewsletterHow to OrderThe Important StuffAuthorize.NetFAQsHardiness ZonesYour PrivacyPrintable Order FormInternational FriendsGarden Club View All Garden Club Welcome to the ClubTip SheetsCurrent EpisodeEpisode 211-220Episode 201-210Episode 191-200Episode 181-190Episode 171-180Episode 161-170Episode 151-160Episode 141-150Episode 131-140Episode 121-130Episode 111-120Episode 101-110Episode 91-100Episode 81-90Episode 71-80Episode 61-70Episode 51-60Episode 41-50Episode 31-40Episode 21-30Episode 11-20Episode 1-10Shipping
Advanced Search
Home
Ordering
Your Privacy
Category Navigation:
Fall 2020
Contact Us
About Us
Fun Stuff
Ordering
Download Our Current Catalogue
Request a Catalogue & Newsletter
How to Order
Fall 2020
Category Navigation:
Fall 2020
Home
Ordering
Your Privacy
Your Privacy
Privacy Policy Statement
We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following list discloses what information we gather from you, how it is used and what systems are in place to ensure that this information remains private:
Information Collection and Use
Botanus Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We collect email addresses of those who communicate with us via email and any information volunteered by visitors on our registration form. The information we collect is used to make contact for marketing purposes and to improve the content of our web site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others.
eNewsletter
If a visitor wishes to subscribe to our eNewsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.  Recipients who no longer wish to receive our eNewsletters may use the opt-out option contained within the eNewsletter or by contacting us at service@botanus.com
Catalogues
If a visitor wishes to receive our catalogues, we ask for their postal address information. If they no longer wish to receive our catalogues, we ask that they send an email to wendy@botanus.com  or call our toll free number: 1-800-672-3413 and provide us with their name and address information. Once received, we will remove the information from our marketing list.
Links
Our web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we at Botanus Inc. are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected on this web site.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and if under any circumstances, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have the choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner.
Questions
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact us. You will find all contact information at the bottom of this statement.
Thank you for visiting us and we hope you return again soon!
